It’s good to share, right?
分享是件好事，对吧？
Growing up as kids we are told to share our toys and not be selfish.
我们小时候就被教导要分享玩具，不能自私。
We also live in an age where discussing our feelings is encouraged.
我们也生活在一个鼓励表达内心感受的时代。
But when does it all become too much?
但凡事过犹不及，何时分享会变得过分呢？
With new crazes trending all the time, such as dance challenges and wearing a pillow as a dress, the question is: when can sharing become oversharing on social media?
如今各种新奇潮流层出不穷，比如跳舞挑战、把枕头当裙子穿，问题也随之而来：在社交媒体上，分享到何种程度就算是过度分享了？
What is oversharing?
什么是过度分享？
The term has become associated with social media, but it isn’t exclusive to this platform.
这个说法如今常和社交媒体挂钩，但并非仅限于这一平台。
Imagine you head to a party and you meet someone.
设想你去参加一场派对，遇到了一个人。
Within five minutes they have divulged intimate details about their life.
短短五分钟内，对方就把自己的私密生活细节和盘托出。
While some of us may try to escape these people, according to marriage therapist Carolyn Cole, this form of oversharing could come from a strong desire to connect with someone.
虽然我们有些人可能会想方设法躲开这类人，但婚姻治疗师卡罗琳·科尔表示，这种过度分享的行为，可能源于一种想要与人建立联结的强烈渴望。
But how does this translate to social media?
但这种行为放到社交媒体上，又会是怎样的情况呢？
Dr Christopher Hand, a lecturer in cyberpsychology, says the more details people disclose, the less sympathy we express when things go wrong.
网络心理学讲师克里斯托弗·汉德博士表示，人们披露的个人细节越多，当他们遭遇不顺时，我们给予的同情就越少。
This could be due to a belief that we attract our own negative experiences the more we share them.
这可能是因为人们认为，分享负面经历的次数越多，就越容易招致更多不顺。
It seems that sadfishing, the idea of searching for sympathy by oversharing, is generally perceived as negative rather than the cry for help it could actually be.
“卖惨式分享”指的是通过过度分享来博取同情，这种行为通常被认为是负面的，而不是一种真实的求助信号。
However, Dr Hand’s research also seems to suggest that the more we post on a platform, the more socially attractive we become – provided that the posts we bang out are positive.
不过汉德博士的研究也表明，只要我们发布的内容都是积极向上的，在社交平台上发帖越频繁，我们的社交吸引力就越强。
Even back in 2015, Gwendolyn Seidman PhD, said that we should avoiding whining and being negative online.
早在2015年，格温多琳·塞德曼博士就曾说过，我们应该避免在网上抱怨和传播负面情绪。
We should also steer clear of showing off, bragging or flexing, as it’s now known – especially about our love lives.
我们还应避免炫耀、吹嘘或如今所说的“晒优越”——尤其是在感情生活方面。
It makes sense – if your date is going ‘that well’, would you really have time to share a photo with text?
这其实很容易理解——如果你的约会进展得“那么顺利”，你真的会有时间发图文分享吗？
So, how can you know if you are oversharing?
那么，怎样才能判断自己是否过度分享了呢？
Well, why not ask your friends in real life.
不妨问问你现实生活中的朋友。
They would probably be more than happy to tell you if your posts about your breakfast or your gripes about your lack of money really are too much.
如果你发的早餐照片，或是吐槽自己缺钱的帖子实在太过了，他们很可能会乐意告诉你。